Chester's Mill is
a place like any other.
At least it used to be
until we were cut off
from the rest of the world
by a mysterious dome.
(cows bellowing)
Invisible, indestructible,
and completely inescapable.
We're trapped.
JULIA: We don't know where it
came from or why it's here,
We don't know where it
but now that we're all trapped
under the dome together,
none of our secrets are safe.
Hi, Jimmy.
BIG JIM:
Rapture is your product, Max.
Which I never could've gotten
off the ground
without my secret ingredient.
Liquid propane.
This town seems
to have a hell of a lot of it.
Duke knew about this?
He didn't want you to know.
LINDA:
Duke?
What the hell were you up to?
MAX:
The pillow talk between you
and Julia is gonna be
done when she finds out
you murdered her husband.
You're not bulletproof, Max.
I have
an insurance policy in place.
Anything bad happens to me,
your secrets still come out.
(plate clatters)
Angie.
The pink stars are falling
in lines.
JOE:
Norrie and I have had
the exact same seizure.
DODEE:
The yagi
stopped working
after Joe and Norrie touched
the dome the other day.
I still don't trust those two.
Guess I was sleepwalking.
But why did
I bring this thing here?
(birds chirping)
몽유병처럼
돌아다니진 않았네
No sleepwalking.
잘했어
Good boy.
뭐야...
What the...
미안
Sorry.
조, 미니 돔 안에
뭐가 있어
Joe, look
what's inside the mini-dome.
와...
Whoa.
- 좀 닥쳐줄래?
- 앤지 언니
Will you guys shut up?
Angie,
알에 뭔가가 찾아왔네요
the egg has a visitor.
저건 애벌레야
That's a caterpillar.
어젯밤엔 분명
없었는데
But it wasn't there last night.
흙 속에 있지
않았을까요?
Maybe it was under the dirt.
우리처럼
돔 안에 갇힌거야
Trapped inside
like the big dome trapped us.
어디선 나왔건 간에
아무일도 생기진 않았네
Wherever it came
from, it was no accident.
검은색, 흰색, 노란색
선무늬가 있어
Look at those black and
white and yellow stripes.
그래?
Yeah?
그리고?
And?
이 에벌레는
제왕나비(monarch butterfly)가 될거야
It's a caterpillar that will
turn into a monarch butterfly.
『The monarch will be crowned.』
"The monarch will be crowned."
줄리아 아줌마가
들었잖아
Julia heard that
숲에서 이 돔을
만졌을 때
when she touched this thing
out in the woods.
- 아줌마는 그게 무슨 의미인지 아실거야
- 아니, 모두 동의하기 전에는
Maybe she'll know what this means.
No, we all agreed
- 이걸 말씀드리면 안돼
- 그래, 하지만 아줌마가
not to tell her that we have it.
Yeah, but she might be
미니돔이 요구하는
네번째 손바닥일 수도 있잖아
the fourth handprint
this mini-dome needs to do...
어떻게 될지는 모르지만
whatever it's gonna do.
혹시...
돔이 없어지는 걸까?
Like... turn off the dome.
좋아, 근데 줄리아 아줌마는
발작 증세가 없으셨잖아
Okay, but Julia
hasn't had seizures.
그렇구나
Yeah.
좋아
Okay.
네번째 손바닥이 누구든지간에
찾아야 돼
We still have to find whoever
the fourth handprint belongs to.
발작까지 일으켰던 사람
Someone with seizures.
조건을 갖춘 사람을
찾아야 돼
We should find others who've had them.
금방 올게요
바비,
일찍 일어났구만?
Hello, Barbie. You're up early.
맥스에 대해서
얘기 좀 하시죠
We need to talk about Max.
어제 맥스가 충분히 행복하진
않았던 것처럼 들리는구만
Sounds like someone's not
too happy to see her yesterday.
그러는 의원님은요?
And you were?
여자는...
일의 일부분이지, 안 그런가?
Woman's a...
piece of work, isn't she?
역시 저보다
노련하시네요
More than I knew.
어...
자네들 둘이
Care to, uh...
어떻게 같이 일하게 됐는지
정확히 알았으면 하는데
share exactly how it is you two
are in business together?
당연히
말씀드려야죠
Sure.
먼저
말씀해 주시면요
Right after you do.
좋아, 내 적의
Well, then,
적은 아군이다
이런건가
enemy of my enemy,
what are we gonna do?
맥스가 우릴
움켜쥐고 있는 한
We can't really move against her
with the dirt she says she has
- 쉽게 움직일 수 없을거야
- 우리가...
on the both of us.
Unless...
잡힌 약점을
제거하지 않는 한 말이죠
we get rid of whatever
this insurance policy is.
그렇지만 그렇게
할 수 있을까요?
But where would that be?
음, 맥스가 말하기를
어떤 집에 묵는다고 했어
Well, she says
she's staying at a house
집주인이 돔 밖에 있는
그런 집
whose owners got trapped
outside the dome.
아뇨, 안돼요
그러기엔 맥스가 너무 영리해요
No. No, she's too smart
for that.
자네도 알겠지만,맥스는
합법적인 회사를 가지고 있네
You know, she's got this, uh,
legitimate real estate company.
'오시리스' 라는
대기업이지
The... Osiris Corporation.
대부분 웨스트레이크에 있는 집들을
사들이는데, 내가 알기로 여기는 거의 없어
Buys homes mostly in Westlake,
but I know she's got a few here.
- 찾아야겠네요
- 그래
That's worth a look.
Yeah.
어떤 집인지 아세요?
You know which houses are hers?
시청 서기 사무실에
기록이 있을거야, 내가...
The town clerk's office
got record. I'll, uh...
확인 해보지
go check it out.
그러니까... 의원님 약점은
없애버리고
You mean, so you can...
you can bury your secrets
제거는 까발려지도록
놔두겠다는 말씀인가요?
and leave mine out there in
the open for the world to see.
내가 자넬
끝장낼거라고 보나?
You think I'd screw you over?
사기꾼이나 진배 없으시잖아요, 짐?
You're a used car salesman, Jim.
좋아, 같이 가지
Sure. We'll go together.
오시리스 회사에서
이동네에 산 집이
Yeah, I'm seeing at least
a dozen houses here
최소 열두채 정도네요
that were purchased
by the Osiris Corporation.
대부분은 일년 이내에 맥스가
리모델링나 재건축 한거야
Most of those Max remodeled
and flipped 'em within a year
그런데...
이건 아니군
but, uh... not this one.
2005년도에 샀는데,부동산 시장에
내놓은 적이 없어
Bought it in 2005.
Never put back on the market.
버드 아일랜드?
It's on Bird Island?
어, Eastpointe 호수
중간에 있는 섬인데
Yeah. It's in the middle
of Lake Eastpointe
돔 안에 있어.
밖에는 별장 몇개 정도 있고
but still under the dome.
Only a few vacation homes
맥스가 우리 비밀을
숨겨놓기에
out there. Not a bad place
to hide whatever it is
나쁘지 않은 장소야
she says she's got on us.
무장은 하고 가야겠죠?
Probably shouldn't go unarmed.
내가 맥스한테 그 총들
다 줬다고 생각하는 건 아니지?
You don't think I'd let Max
have all the guns, do you?
어 어~
둘이서 뭐해요?
Uh-oh. What
are you two doing?
내가 걱정해야 되는 일인가?
Should I be worried?
아니, 그냥 마을 일
얘기하고 있었어
No, just some town business.
알다시피 마을에는
네가 상관없는 일들도
You know, there are things
going on here that don't
- 많거든
- 뭐, 어쨌든
involve you.
Mm, for now anyway.
자, 이거
Here you go.
에스프레소?
"Espresso"?
다크초콜렛이랑,
섬유유연제?
"Dark chocolate,
silk-infused conditioner"?
내가 좀 사치스러워서 말이지
I like my luxuries.
이 망할 돔에 갇혔다고 해서
내가 그런 사치를
Just because this damn dome
came down doesn't mean
못부릴 이유가 없잖아
I'm gonna do without.
집도 좀 외져 있어서 말이지
내가 말한거 구해 줄 수
There's abandoned houses.
I'm sure you can find
- 있지?
- 아니, 네 쇼핑질 도와주진 않을거야
some of that stuff.
No, I'm not... I'm not doing your shopping.
아니, 지미 시켜
No. Just Jimmy.
너는 나랑 다른 일
처리해야지
You and I have other business
to attend to.
그게 싫으면,
Or if you want,
너네 더러운 비밀
다 까발려서
I can reveal
all your dirty laundry
어떻게 좆되나
지켜보시던지
and then we can see
how that goes.
바비, 가요
Barbie, let's go.
- 뭐야 이게?
- 번개 치는 소리가 나던데
What the hell was that?
It sounded like thunder.
도디...
Dodee...
UNDER THE DOME
SEASON 1 EPISODE 10
Let the Games Begin
도디?
Dodee?
괜찮아요?
Are you all right?
여기가 어디야?
Where am I?
병원이에요
저희가 모셔왔어요
We're at the clinic.
We brought you here.
어.. 나한테
무슨 일이 있었던거지?
Well, what happened to me?
기억 안나세요?
You don't remember?
기억나...
전기가..
- I remember...
- electricity.
방송국 밖에...
발전기 때문인가?
Was it... was it the generator
outside the radio station?
네...
맞아요
Yeah, that's right.
저희가 발전기 옆에서
발견했어요
We found you by your generator
outside the radio station.
지나가는데 이상한
소리가 나서 들렀다가
We were passing by
and we heard a noise.
손에 화상 입으신거
발견한거에요
And then we found you
with that burn on your hand.
그래.. 맞아..
내 생각에...
Yeah. Yeah,
I-I guess
그게 마지막
기억인 거 같아
that's the last thing
I remember
- 거기에서...
- 도디!
- was, was being there.
- Dodee.
이게 어떻게 된 일이야?
What... happened to her?
발전기에 감전되신거 같아요
We think she got zapped
by a generator.
의식을 잃었었니?
Did she lose consciousness?
20분 정도요
For, like, 20 minutes.
잘했다, 병원에 데려다 줘서
고맙다 얘들아
All right, well, thanks
for bringing her in.
내가 잘 간호할게
I'll take good care of her.
아담스 언니
Nurse Adams.
최근에 발작 일으켜서
온 사람 있나요?
Do you know anyone else
who's had seizures lately?
조나 저 말구요
Besides Joe and I.
너 학교 다닐 때
그런 후론 없었어 앤지
Not since your tenth grade
dance, Angie.
무슨 말이야?
What does that mean?
뭐 잘못된거에요?
What's wrong?
누나!
Angie!
계세요?
Hello?
아무도 안계세요?
Anyone here?
누구 안계세요~
Hello?
계세요?
- 린다!
- 왔어요?
Linda.
Hey.
어... 바비 찾고 있는데,
여기 있나요?
Uh, I'm just looking
for Barbie. Is he around?
못 봤어요
I haven't seen him.
무슨 일 있어요?
What's going on?
요전에, 안드레아 그리넬 씨랑
A while back, you spoke
with Andrea Grinnell
프로판가스 창고에
이상한 점이 있다고
about some weird stuff going on
얘기하셨었죠, 그렇죠?
at the propane
warehouse, right?
네
Yeah.
그거 더 추적하셨었나요?
Did you ever follow up on it?
솔직히, 안드레아가 좀
이상하다고 생각했어요
Honestly I thought
she was kind of loopy.
그러다 이 난리가 됐고,
잊고 있었죠 뭐...
And then everything went to hell
and I just forgot about it.
왜요?
Why?
안드레아는 이상한게
아니었어요
Andrea wasn't so loopy
after all.
이거 좀 보세요
Look at this.
이 여자가
누군지를 모르겠어요
I don't know who this woman is.
저기 오시네요
Here comes
듀크 서장님
Duke.
저 여자가 서장님을
돈으로 조종했군요
She's handing him money.
랩쳐라고,
프로판으로 만든 마약에
All of which has something
to do with...
관련된 일을 하셨던거 같아요
a drug being made
using propane called Rapture.
서장님이 마약에 관련됐다고
생각하시는거에요?
You think Duke
was involved with drugs?
코긴스 목사님도요
Reverend Coggins, too.
코긴스가 증거를 없애려고
서장님 집을 불태운거 같아요
I think Coggins burned down
Duke's house to hide evidence.
지금은 두분 다
돌아가셨고
Now they're both dead, and...
저 혼자 여기서
I've driven myself crazy
미친듯이 해답을 찾고 있네요
searching this place
for an answer.
서장님이 보통 분이
아닌건 알잖아요
You knew Duke better
than anyone.
숨겨 놓은거라도 찾았어요?
Where else
would he stash something?
서장님이 관심 있었던건
낚시랑 술,
All he really cared
about was fly-fishing, bourbon,
그리고 저 모자가
전부에요
and that hat.
낚시 도구함은
집에서 불타버렸고,
The tackle box was
burned in the house,
술은 남기는 법이
절대 없었어요
he never left a
bottle unfinished
그리고 모자는
꼭 쓰고 다니셨는데...
and he never took
that hat off his head.
아, 이런게 여기에...
Well, hello there.
무슨 열쇠일까요?
What do you unlock?
안전 금고
Safe-deposit box.
채스터스 밀 은행
Bank of Chester's Mill.
제가 운전할게요
I'll drive.
그래,
그럴 줄 알았다 이놈아
Yeah, you're not acting
suspicious.
어딜 그리 급하게 가시나?
Where you going so fast?
- 아무데도요
- 뭐?
Nowhere.
Huh?
- 아우!
- 입 닥쳐
Ow!
Shut up before I add
절도가 확실하면
damaging police property
to what you obviously
가중처벌 시켜버릴거야
ripped off from someone.
- 소금?
- 그래, 편의점에서 훔쳐야 됐어
- Salt? - So, I might've shoplifted it
from the convenience store.
- 근데 왜 소금을 훔쳐?
- 장난치냐?
Yeah, but why steal that?
You kidding?
시멘트 공장에 들어가려면
현금보다 값어치 있는게 필요하다고
Better than cash if you want
to get into the cement factory.
한마디 충고할까, 바비
Word of advice, Barbie.
시청에 짐이랑 옹기종기 모여서
뭘 하는지는 모르겠지만
Whatever you and Big Jim were
huddling about at Town Hall...
조심해
be careful.
짐을 믿으면 안돼
You can't trust him.
내가 어떻게 당신을 믿나요~
뭐 이런거야?
You mean kind of like
how I can trust you?
바비, 난 너한테
거짓말 한 적 없어
I have never lied to you, Dale.
나도 너처럼
생각했음 좋겠네
I'd like to think
the same about you.
그래, 처리해야 할 일이
도대체 뭐야?
So what's this business
we need to attend to?
이 사람들 교회에
기도하러 가는거 같진 않은데
I'm guessing these people aren't
here for a church service.
아냐. 그냥 좀 어른들 놀이
즐기러 가는거지
No, just a little
adult entertainment.
돔에 갇히고 9일동안
뭘 했겠어?
It's been, what, nine days
since the dome came down?
TV도 안 나오지,
인터넷도 안 되지
There's been no TV,
there's been no Internet,
재미라고는 눈꼽만큼도
찾을 수가 없잖아
there's been no fun at all.
그래, 그래서 돈 버는
냄새를 맡으셨나?
Right, so now you smell
an opportunity
술, 도박, 매춘
그런걸로?
for your usual booze,
cards, brothels.
야
Hey.
매춘은 절대 한 적 없어
I don't deal in
prostitution ever.
알겠어?
You got that?
빨리 와
Come on.
내 거친 세상에
온 걸 환영해
Welcome to my brave new world.
한글자막 : 차이콥스키™ by DOTAL
배 포 : DC 기타미국드라마 갤러리
영문자막 : honeybunny
누구시죠?
Who are you?
함부로 들어와서
죄송합니다 부인, 저는...
Sorry for the intrusion,
ma'am. I-I'm...
잠깐,
빅 짐 레니?
Wait. Big Jim Rennie?
자동차 판매하시는?
From the car commercials?
"싼 가격으로 큰 이윤을!"
♪ Small price, big savings. ♪
- 네, 접니다
- 뭐, 거의
That's me.
Well, then...
무단 침입이네요
it's hardly an intrusion.
당신 광고 좋아해요
딴 사람들처럼 TV에서
I like your ads.
You don't scream from the TV
- 소리지르진 않잖아요
- 그건 제 스타일이 아닙니다
like the rest of 'em.
That's not my style, ma'am.
편하게 '아가사' 라고
부르세요
Please, call me Agatha.
아가사, 만나뵈서
반갑습니다
Agatha, nice to meet you.
- 여기 주인이세요?
- 아뇨
This your house?
No.
전 그냥 관리인이에요
I'm just the caretaker.
정원손질 같은거 하죠
Gardening and such.
주인이...
For, um...
맥신 시그레이브 인가요?
for Maxine Seagrave?
맥신이란 사람은
몰라요
Don't know a Maxine.
주인은 올리버 러클랜드란
분이에요
The owner's Oliver Luckland.
그분은 보트 타러
섬 반대편에 가셨어요
He's on the other side of the
island, tending to his boat.
제가 여기 온
이유는,
I came here because,
차 파는 것보다
더 중요한 일로 왔습니다
more important
than selling cars,
저는 채스터스 밀 시
시의원 입니다
I'm a councilman
for Chester's Mill,
그래서 이렇게
위험한 시기에
and I'm making my way around
to see if our citizens
우리 시민들이 필요한게 없나
둘러보고 있는 중입니다
need anything
in this time of crisis.
네, 좀 쇼킹하죠?
Yes, it is shocking, isn't it?
그래도 여기는
평화롭고 조용해서 좋네요
I'm glad to be here
amid the peace and quiet.
러클랜드 씨가 나가신지
오래됐나요?
Is Mr. Luckland gonna be long?
어, 기다려도 될까요?
Uh, c-can I wait for him?
안에서요?
Inside?
맛있는 차 한 잔
준비하죠
We'll have a nice cup of tea.
고맙습니다
Great.
내 사업장 와보니까 어때?
What do you think
of my grand opening?
전에 하던 거보다
훨씬 작네, 그치?
I think it's a lot smaller
than you're used to, isn't it?
아, 곧 마을 전체가
이렇게 될거야
Oh, in time I'll have
the whole town here.
어떻게 이 많은걸
다 모은거야?
How'd you put
all this together?
지난 주까지는 그냥
뭉개고 있었는데
By not sitting on my hands
for the past week.
이 사람들 중에 몇명이 전에
나한테 빚을 졌더라고
Some of these people
owed me from before.
그래서 네 명단에서
얼굴 비슷한 몇명은
I'm sure you'll recognize
a few familiar faces
알아볼거라고
확신했지
from your collection duties.
식구들 먹이려고
달걀이 필요해서
Say somebody needs eggs
for his family
여분의 베터리를 가지고 오지
그리고 여기로 와서
and he's got some spare
batteries. He comes in here,
운을 시험하는거지
이기면, 달걀 가져가고
tries his luck.
If he wins, he trades up.
지면...
내가 다 갖는거고
If he loses... I win.
아... 주민들은 이미
물물교환을 하고 계셨구만
Uh...
people are already bartering
그래, 필요하니까
around town.
Yeah, that's for needs.
여기서는
어쩔수 없어
In here, it's about vices.
왜 그래
Come on.
다 마찬가지야
너도 그렇고
Everybody's got 'em. Even you.
생존이 내기라는 걸
아셨구만
You realize survival's at stake.
그래,
전부 내꺼야
Yeah, mine.
이 거지같은 데에
갇힌 이상
If I'm gonna be trapped
in this hellhole,
살아남으려면
뭐든지 할거야
I am gonna live
as well as I can.
왜 그래?
What's going on?
얘기하고 싶지 않아
I don't want to talk about it.
언니, 제발
언니 좀 이상해요
Angie, come on,
you're obviously upset.
주니어가
네번째 손인거 같아
I think Junior
is the fourth hand.
- 농담이지?
- 10학년 댄스 파티 때였어
You're joking.
My tenth grade dance.
주니어가 기절해서
병원에 실려갔는데
Junior got rushed to the clinic
for passing out.
모두들 술 때문이라고는 했지만,
And everyone said it was
because he had been drinking,
아담스 간호사는
발작이라고 했단 말이야
but Nurse Adams just said
someone had a seizure.
하지만
주니어 형일리가 없어
But it can't be Junior.
그 형은 좀
정신나간 거 같다고
That guy weirds me out.
나라고 좋은 줄 알아?
You think that I'm happy
about it?
걔가 나한테 그 말 하고나서?
After what he did to me?
무슨 뜻이야?
What does that mean?
돔이 생기고 나서
You remember
how you couldn't find me
한동안 네가 나
못 봤던거 기억나?
after the dome came down?
잠깐
Wait.
주니어랑 같이 있었어?
You were with him?
형 말로는 누나
본 적이 없다던데
He said he hadn't
even seen you.
응
Hmm.
자발적으로..
그런게 아니야
It wasn't... voluntary.
뭐?
What?
걔가 날 가둬놓고 말하기를
돔이 나를 아프게 한다고 했어
He kept saying that the dome
was making me sick
그리고 나으려면
and the only way that I could
자기랑 같이
있어야 한다더라
get better is
if I stayed with him.
그래서 언니를
납치한거에요?
So he kidnapped you?
He had these reasons
- 그 얘기를 하는데, 미친거 같더라고 그래서...
- 어디있어?
that seemed really weird then, but...
Where is he?
- 그새끼 죽여버릴거야
- 안돼 조, 걔가 죽으면,
'Cause I'm gonna kill him.
No, Joe, if anyone's gonna kill him,
- 내가 죽인게 돼
- 내가 하기 전엔 아니지
it's gonna be me.
Not before I do.
- 누나, 비켜!
- 조, 그만해!
Get out of my way, Angie!
Joe, stop!
그만둬요!
둘 다!
Stop it! Both of you,
그만!
stop!
그 새끼가 언니를
납치했다면,
Look, I'm all
for kicking Junior's ass
그 새끼 좆되게 만드는데
내 모든 걸 바칠게
if he kidnapped you, Ange.
근데, 그 새끼가
네 번째 손이라면...
But if he's the fourth hand...
그래...
Yeah.
I guess
네 말이 맞아
you're right.
언니, 주니어가 같은 방식으로
발작을 일으킨거 확신해요?
Are you sure what Junior had
way back then was a seizure?
응
Yeah.
그리고 걔라고 생각한 이유가
그거 하나 뿐이 아니야
And that's not the only reason
I think it's him.
그거 말고 또?
It's not?
보여줄게 있어
I should show you something.
돔이 생기고 나서
전부 급하게
Looks like everyone left
the bank in a hurry
은행을 뜬거 같네요
after the dome came down.
은행 돈
전부 챙겨가도
We could take
all the cash in here,
아무 의미없는 짓이에요
it wouldn't mean a thing.
결혼생활 망치고,
And to think it was money
that ruined
남편 도망간 것도
전부 돈 때문이에요
my marriage and forced my husband to run off.
Is that
그래서 피터가
떠난거에요?
why Peter left town?
은행잔고가
줄줄 새고
After draining
our bank accounts
집이 압류 당한 것도
and putting our home
in foreclosure
남편 도박빚 갚느라
그런거에요
to pay off his gambling debts.
사실 뭔가 잘못됐다는 걸
알고는 있었지만,
I think deep down I knew
something was wrong.
제 눈으로
보고 싶지 않았어요
I just didn't want to see it.
젠장
Damn it.
여기 어디 근처에
There must be a key
안전금고실 열쇠가
있을거에요
to the safe-deposit room
around here somewhere.
린다, 이중에 하나...
Hey, maybe one of these...
열렸어요!
Got it!
워~ 이게 누구신가
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
빅 주니어 레니
Big Junior Rennie.
그냥 주니어라고 불러요
Just Junior.
Hmm.
안에서 무슨 일이
벌어지는 거에요?
What's going on inside?
- 알 필요 없어
- 던컨, 제발
Nothing for you.
Come on, Duncan.
- 저도 이거 가져왔어요
- 너 지금은 경찰이잖아
I got these.
Look, I know you're a cop now.
그 말은 넌 여기
못 들어온다는 거지
Means you don't belong here.
이것봐,
나도 그 목록에 있는거
Hey, I got
갖고 있어
what's on the list.
들여보내 줘
Let me in.
자,자 얼른 들어가요
Let's go, let's go.
오우~ 예~!
Oh, yes!
내가 이겼어!
I won!
봤지?
즐거워 하잖아
See? People have fun,
저 사람들은 승수 챙기고,
난 위에서 살짝 빨아가고,
they collect their winnings,
I skim a little off the top,
- 모두들 행복해지지
- 그래서 나한테 원하는게 뭐야?
everybody's happy.
So what do you need me for?
돔이 생기고 나서
이 형편없는 마을은 많은 혼돈이 생겼어
Lot of chaos in this crummy town
since it all went to hell,
그래도 수없이 반복해서
들리는 단 한가지는
but the one thing I've heard
over and over again is,
"바비는 진짜 나쁜놈이다."
라는거야
"That Barbie is
a real badass."
네가 메인 이벤트야, 바비
You're the main event.
아니, 안돼
난 싸우지 않을거야
No, no, no, no, no.
I am not gonna fight. You must've
어제 했던 얘기를
전부 잊었나 본데
forgotten everything
we talked about yesterday then.
네가 피터 셤웨이를
어떻게 죽였나 하는걸
About how you killed
Peter Shumway.
줄리아가 듣게되면
널 얼마나 미워할까?
And how Julia would hate
hearing about that.
게다가, 기억날지 모르겠는데
동창이었던
Besides, think of it
as a reunion because...
네 상대 빅터 롤린스,
맞나?, 기억나?
you remember your opponent
Victor Rawlins, right?
그래, 쟤는 도박으로
Yeah, he gambled his way
두어달 전에
전부 다 날렸어
down the drain
a couple months ago. He lost
아내도 잃고, 아이들도 잃고,
인생 아주 좆됐지
his wife, his kids,
his whole life really.
아니, 네가 채권자잖아, 그렇지?
No, you're his bookie, okay?
- 내가 아니라
- 그래,하지만
Not me.
Yeah, but you were the one knocking
네가 저 놈한테서
돈을 받아다 줬잖아
on his door forcing him
to pay up.
이번에는 넌 총도 없고,
빅터도
Only this time you don't have
a gun and Victor
진짜로 동등하게 싸울 준비가
된 것처럼 보이는데
really looks ready
to even the score.
설탕 넣어요, 짐?
You take sugar, Big Jim?
네, 부인
Yes, ma'am.
러클랜드 씨가..
Sure Mr. Luckland
제가 이렇게 온거
불쾌해 하실까요?
doesn't, uh, mind us being here?
오, 아뇨
Oh, no.
올리버는 손님들 오시면
항상 친절하게 대해주셨어요
Oliver's as hospitable
as they come.
어.. 저는 이 집이
I was, uh,
under the impression...
다른 사람 소유라고
생각했었거든요
somebody else owned this house.
아뇨, 그분 집이
확실해요
No, I'm certain he does.
집에 오래 안계실 뿐이죠
But he's not here much.
다른 소유지에
더 오래 계시거든요
He spends a lot of time out
at his other properties.
그래서 제가 이렇게
여기서 관리하는거에요
That's why he has me
taking care of things.
운이 좋은 분이네요,
아가사 같이 좋은 이웃이 계셔서
Sure is lucky to have a neighbor
like you, Agatha.
내 딸 맥신이에요
That's my daughter Maxine.
자 이제 등 뒤에 있는
총 빼놓고
Now do me a favor
and drop that gun
내 부탁 좀
들어주실까
that's tucked
in the back of your belt.
천천히
Slowly.
알겠습니다
Okay.
맥신은 그렇게 자란 건
Maxine didn't learn
아빠한테 배운게 아냐
to be the way she is
from her father.
메인 이벤트로
누가 준비 중일까요?
Who's ready for the main event?
자, 오래 기다리셨습니다
All right, all right,
well, your wait is over,
빅터 롤린스 대
because here it is:
Victor Rawlins versus
스페셜 포스 출신의 베테랑
데일 "바비" 바바라!
your special forces veteran
Dale "Barbie" Barbara!
룰은 간단합니다
좆도 없어
The rules are simple:
there aren't any.
라운드도 없고,
시간제한도 없어
There's no rounds,
no time limits.
질 때까지
싸우면 돼
You fight till you lose.
최고의 남자가
승리하기를
May the best man win.
책임질 거면,
날 실망시켜 보시지
Disappoint me at your own risk.
앉아
Sit.
편하게 있어
Make yourself comfortable.
맥신은 해 떨어지기 전에는
안 오니까
Maxine should be here
after sundown.
내일 올 수도 있고
Or maybe tomorrow.
그럼 라이플을
오래 들고 계셔야겠네요
Well, that's a long time
to hold a rifle on someone.
졸리지만 않으면 좋겠네,
어쩌면 방아쇠 당길 수도 있거든
I hope I don't get drowsy,
somehow pull the trigger.
나 기억 안나지, 그렇지?
You don't remember me, do you?
네, 힌트 좀...
Well, give me a hint.
우리 고등학교 때
같은 반이었어
We were in the same
high school class.
뭐, 난 자퇴 했지만
Well, until I dropped out.
내가 자퇴생 기억하는 건
딱 한명인데...
There's only one student
I remember dropping out.
걔 이름이...
클레어였어
Her name was Claire.
개명했지
I changed my name.
네가 기억할 거라
생각하는데
I'm sure you can imagine why.
꽤 유명한
스캔들이었거든
It was quite the scandal.
너 임신했었지
You got pregnant.
맥신이랑
With Maxine.
난 겨우
열 여섯이었어
I was only 16,
사람들이 내 인생은
끝났다고 낙인을 찍었지
and people treated me like
my life was already over.
- 그렇지 않아
- 난 추방자였어
That's not true.
I was a pariah.
내 딸을 먹여살릴
방법이 없었지...
I had no way
to support my daughter...
몸을 파는 수밖에...
...except by starting
to let men in my bed.
사람들은 돌아서서,
날 공개적으로 모욕했지
Men who would turn around
and publicly shame me
부도덕한 년이라고
말이야
for being the immoral one.
여전히 여기 있네
Still you're here.
악취가 풍기는 곳에서
충분히 도망쳐왔지
Far enough away to keep the
stink out of our hair.
맥신은 웨스트 레이크로
이사갔어
Maxine moved to Westlake,
그리고 나도 딸이랑
가까이 있으려고 여기로 왔지
and I came here
to be close to her.
하지만 우린 채스터스 밀의
진면모를 잊지 못했어
But neither of us will ever
forget the real Chester's Mill.
친절한 웃음 뒤에
송곳니를 드러내는 것들
The sharp teeth behind
the friendly smile.
그래, 웃음 뒤에는
이빨이 있지
Well, there are teeth
behind the smile.
일을 해결하기 위해서는
어쩔 수 없어
It's the only way
to get things done.
프로판 가스 같은 걸 말하는거지?
Like the propane, you mean?
딸이 모든 걸 말해줬어
My daughter tells me
everything.
내가 원하는 모든 증거를 줬어
너, 듀크...
Gave me every bit of evidence
I need on you and Duke,
그 더러운 목사 코긴스까지
that nutty Reverend Coggins.
그래서...
So...
네 딸이 바비에 대해서도
얘기해줬겠지?
she must have told you
about Barbie, too, huh?
그럼~
Oh, yeah.
다리 부러진 것도
About him breaking legs.
셤웨이 박사 죽인 것도
Killing that Dr. Shumway.
걔가 여기에서 꼼짝 못하는 것도
그리 놀라운 일은 아니지
It's no surprise
he got stuck here.
이 마을에는...
This town...
최악의 인간들만
끌어들이는 힘이 있지
it always has been a magnet
for the worst of humanity...
자네 아들처럼 말이지
like your son.
주니어도 지 애미처럼
Junior's turning out
미쳐가고 있지, 안그래?
to be just as crazy as his mama,
isn't he?
- 입 닥쳐
- 앉아!
Shut your mouth!
Sit down!
안그러면 총알로
가슴팍을 뚫어줄테니깐
Or I'll put a bullet
through your chest!
누구 죽여본 적 있나,
아가사?
Have you ever killed someone,
Agatha?
네 눈물겨운 스토리 잘 들었는데,
내 말은 누군가를
I mean, I know you got your sob
story and all, but have you ever
진짜 죽여본 적 있냐 이거야
really rolled up your sleeves
and murdered someone?
멈춰
Stop.
난 그런 적 있거든
'Cause I have.
네 눈에 그 모든 분노가
담겨 있어도
And even with all that
hate in your eyes,
살의는 안 보인단 말이지
I'm not seeing what
it takes to kill.
그러니,
해봐 어디
But go ahead...
내 말이 틀렸다고
증명해보라고
prove me wrong.
자, 이제 네 모녀한테
한방 먹일 차례인가
Now we're gonna do something
about your family.
여기가 주니어 어머님이
쓰시던 방이에요?
So this place belonged
to Junior's mother?
응. 어제 주니어가
여기 데려와서...
Yeah. He brought me
here yesterday...
이걸 보여줬어
to show me this.
분홍 별
Pink stars.
이 그림이랑
걔가 발작을 일으켰다는 사실?
This and the fact
that he's had seizures?
그래도 그 새끼
죽여버릴거야
I'm still gonna kill him.
그 새끼는 싸이코야
The guy's a psycho.
아냐, 조. 그건 우리가
원하는게 아냐
No, Joe, it doesn't matter
what we want.
돔이 원하는거지
It matters what the dome wants.
이제 주니어를
찾아야겠네
Now we just need
to find Junior.
나 여기 있는데
I'm right here.
그 그림 가지고
뭣들 하는거야?
What the hell
are you doing with that?
이 개새끼!
You son of a bitch!
조! 안돼!
ANGIE
Joe! No!
- 안돼! 하지마!
- 조! 안돼!
No-no-no-no!
Joe, no!
- 그만 둬!
- 날 공격해?
- Stop!
- You're attacking me?
너도 불법침입한
놈들 중에 하나야
You're the one
who's trespassing.
네가 우리 누나
납치했잖아!
You kidnapped my sister!
- 주니어!
- 아빠하고 약속했잖아,
Junior!
You promised my dad
아무한테도
말 안하기로
you wouldn't tell
anyone about that.
그렇게 했어!
단지 지금
I had to!
Just like you have
- 네 도움이 필요한거야!
- 뭐?
to help us now!
What?
먼저 놔줘!
놔줘! 놔줘!
Look, first let him go!
Let him go! Let him go!
주니어, 안돼!
놔줘!
Junior, no!
Let him...!
내가 왜 도와줘야 하는데
Why should I help you
with anything?
난 널 믿어서 여기까지
I brought you here
데려왔는데
because I trusted you.
여긴 엄마가 유일하게
나한테 남겨주신 곳이야
These are the only things
I have left of my mother.
주니어, 어제
네가 그랬잖아
Junior, you said yesterday
더 큰 뭔가가
오고 있다고, 그렇지?
that something bigger
is going on, right?
우리 모두를 이어주는
어떤 일이 생길 거라고 했잖아
Something that connects
all of us to what's happening?
그래서, 뭐?
Yeah. So?
우리랑 같이
우리집 헛간에 가줘
So I need you to come with us
to our barn.
왜?
Why?
왜냐하면...
Because...
우리 모두...
all of us...
우리 네명이...
이어져 있어
...the four of us--
are connected
뭔가...
to something...
놀라운 거야
amazing.
나가!
Get out there!
바비, 힘내!
Come on, Barbie! Whoo!
끝내버려!
Finish it!
패배자!
Loser!
끝내버려!
Finish it!
Stay down, you bum!
Stay down!
You're out! Stay down!
일어서
Get up.
야 이 덩치만 큰 놈아!
Hey, big man. Hey!
네 부인이랑 자식만 남는건
아무도 원하지 않아
No wonder your wife and kids
left you.
있는 힘껏 날 쳐!
Hit me as hard as you can.
Get up!
Come on, Barbie! Seriously?!
Let's go!
Get back up!
최고의 남자가
이긴거 같네
I guess the best man won.
예상대로 넌
싸움을 포기했어
You threw the fight
just like I knew you would.
좆까, 죽기살기로 했어
Oh, like hell I did.
여기 모두가
우리 영웅한테 베팅을 했지
Everyone here bet on the hero
그리고 등골 빠졌어
and lost their asses.
난 빅터한테 걸었어...
I bet on Victor...
널 잘 아니까
because I know you.
내가 이기는 거 빼곤
뭐든 할거라는거
And I know that you would do
anything except let me win.
이거네요,
서장님 안전금고
Here it is, Duke's
safe-deposit box.
세상에...
Oh, my God.
그게 뭔데요?
What is that?
서장님이
심박 조정기를 달고
When Duke woke up
from his heart surgery
심장 수술 후에
일어나셨을 때
when he had his
pacemaker put in,
제가 이걸 드렸어요
I gave him this.
의사들이
심장 위치를 찾을 때
I told him the doctors found it
필요할거라고
말씀드렸는데
where his heart
should have been.
이걸 가지고
계신 줄 몰랐어요
I can't believe he kept it.
편지도 있네요
There's a letter here.
못 읽겠어요...
I can't.
읽어주세요
You read it.
관계 당사자 앞
"To whom it may concern,
제 이름은 듀크 퍼킨스이고,
채스터스 밀의 보안관입니다
"my name is Duke Perkins,
Sheriff of Chester's Mill,
제가 고향이라고 부를 수 있는
유일한 곳이죠
"the only place I've ever been
able to call home.
그게 제가 했던 일들의
이유 입니다
That's the reason I did
what I did."
서장님 진술서네요
His confession.
19년 전, 저는 마약으로
제 아들을 잃었습니다
"19 years ago
I lost my son to drugs.
저는 마약중독으로 죽어가는 아들을
무기력하게 바라봐야만 했습니다
I watched helplessly as he was
swept away by his addiction."
알고 있었어요?
Did you know this?
한번도 그런 말씀
하신 적 없어요
He never talked about it.
앞으로 제 손으로
할 수 있는 유일한 일은
"The only thing that kept me
제 손으로 저 자신에게 한
약속을 지키는 것이었습니다
"from turning my gun
on myself was a promise I made:
그건 제가 할 수 있는
모든 것을 동원해
"to do everything I could
채스터스 밀에서 마약을
추방하는 것이었습니다
"to keep drugs out
of Chester's Mill.
그래서 저는
맥신 시그레이브란 이름의
"So I made a deal with a devil
악마와
계약을 맺었습니다
by the name of
Maxine Seagrave."
비디오에 찍힌 그 여자에요
That's got to be the woman
in the video.
계약은 간단했습니다
"The deal was simple:
the town bought
'비상대비용 물자'로 위장한
액화 프로판 가스를
"the liquid propane she needed
그녀가 원하는만큼
마을에서 구매했습니다
"under the guise
of 'emergency reserves'
그래서 DEA는
눈치채지 못했고,
"so the DEA
wouldn't look into it,
그녀는 시의 금고를 지탱할 수 있을 만큼
돈을 충분히 지급해줬습니다
"and she'd pay us enough
to shore up the town's coffers
그리고 그녀는
채스터스 밀 밖으로 그녀의 마약과
"and keep her drugs--
all drugs--
다른 모든 마약을 실어 갔습니다
out of Chester's Mill."
서장님이 우릴 구하신거에요
He did it to save us.
저는 이 마을의 모든 주민들을 위해
제 영혼을 팔았습니다
"I sold my soul
for the people of this town.
제 아들과 같은 사람
"People like my son.
린다 에스키벌 같은 사람들을 위해 말이죠
"People like Linda Esquivel.
이 계약에는 두 사람이 더 있습니다
"There were two other people
in this deal:
모든 불법적인 과정을 세탁했던
레스터 코긴스,
"Lester Coggins...
who laundered our proceeds,
그리고 우리 마을을 위해
프로판을 구매했다고
"and the man who was the front,
전면에 나서서
연설했던
"saying he was buying
the propane for our town:
빅 짐 레니
Big Jim Rennie."
당연히 그 인간도
연관됐겠죠
Of course he was involved.
왜 저한테 말씀 안하셨을까요?
Why didn't Duke tell me?
당신을 사랑했으니까요
Because he loved you.
피터도 같은 이유로
제가 말 안했을거에요
Maybe the same reason
Peter didn't tell me.
후레쉬 좀 비춰주실래요?
You think you could hold
a flashlight for me?
바비랑 얘기해야겠어요
I need to talk to Barbie.
그래,
So,
나랑 뭘 할 계획이신가?
what are you planning
on doing with me?
내 경험상,
약간의 인내심만 있으면
My experience has been
that with a little patience,
세상은 올바로 행동하는 길을
보여준다는 거지
the world reveals
the right course of action.
너는 세상이 그냥 널 찾아와
준다고 생각하는거지, 안그래?
You think the world is just
looking out for you, don't you?
누구든, 뭐든간에
숨어있기만 하면
As if whoever and whatever
is behind that curtain
커튼이 널 위해서
펼쳐진다 이거지
is pulling strings
just for you.
커튼 뒤에는
아무것도 없어
There's nothing
behind that curtain
- 어둠 뿐이지
- 앉아
but darkness.
Sit down.
아가사!
Agatha!
Hey!
짐, 도와줘!
Help me!
제발...
도와줘
Help me, please...
손이 묶여있잖아
My hands are tied.
짐, 제발
Jim, please.
도와줘!
Help me!
뭐하고 있는거야?
What are you doing?
도와줘!
Help!
살려줘!
Help me!
안돼!
No!
도와줘!
Help! Help!
힘내, 바비
Cheer up, Barbie.
하우스가 언제나
이긴다는 거 알잖아
You know the house always wins.
오늘밤은 더 성공적이었잖아,
안그래?
Tonight was rather successful,
wasn't it?
내가 이겼어
I won.
넌...
날 도운거고
You... helped me win.
난 항상
알고 있었어
I've always known--
우리가...
and I think
you have, too--
존나 좋은 팀을
만들거란 걸
that we make a damn good team.
이 돔이 계속 있는 한
And as long as this dome
is around,
우리가 이 마을을
집어삼킬 수 있을거야
I could see us making this town
our playground.
사람들이 네가 승리하도록
두진 않을거야
These people aren't
gonna let you win.
지금이야 너한테 뭔가 빚진 것들이
있어서 좀 쥐고 있겠지만
Yeah, you got a few
that owe you something now,
결국에는
but at the end of the day,
원하는 것처럼 엄청나게
커지진 않을거야
that ain't a whole
hell of a lot.
그래, 더 많은 사람들이
나한테 빚을 지고
Yeah, until more people owe me
그 후에 내가 걔네 꼭대기에
올라서면 돼
and then more people
on top of them.
내가 원하는 대로 살거야, 바비
I'll live
the way I want, Barbie.
우린, 우리가 원하는대로 살거라고
We will live the way we want.
더 얻을 수 없다면 어떡할래?
What if you don't get more?
어?
Huh?
위스키가 더이상 없으면?
You don't get your whiskey?
나를 더이상
다룰 수 없으면?
You don't get me?
그러면, 전부
불사지를거야
Then I'll burn the place down.
뭐하게?
What are you doing?
내가 해야 될 일
What I should've done
좀 전에...
a while ago.
오, 내가 빡돌길
바라진 않겠지, 데일?
Oh, you do not want
to piss me off, Dale.
피터 셤웨이의 시체가
아직 네가 묻은
Not when under your feet
땅속에 있는데,
이러면 안되지
lies a body belonging
to Peter Shumway.
내가 시키는대로 하던가
You do everything I say
그 시체에 관한
진실이 밝혀지던가
or the truth about
him will come out.
이것 봐...
바비...
That's... See, that's
the old Barbie.
우린 끝났어, 맥스
We're finished, Max.
여기서 볼 줄 몰랐네
Didn't expect to see you here.
제가 여기 있을 줄 몰랐네요
I didn't expect to be here.
얘기 좀 하죠
You and I need to talk.
그래
Sure.
들어 와
Come on in.
저녁 대접 좀 하지
I'll even cook us up
some dinner.
미디움 레어 괜찮아?
How's something
medium-rare sound?
서까지 가주시죠
Actually, let's do this
at the station.
나 오늘 힘들었어, 린다
I've had a hell of a day, Linda.
무슨 얘기를 하려는 건지는
모르겠지만
Whatever it is you think
we need to talk about,
아침에 하면 안될까?
it can wait till the morning.
내가 마을에서...
Think I've, uh,
존경받고 있다는 걸
고려해주는게 안될까?
earned that much respect
in this town, right?
지금은 그냥
갈 수 있지만
Come by first thing,
다시 오게되면
or I come back
수갑을 차셔야 할거에요
and these cuffs
don't stay on my belt.
얘기할 게 있어요
I need to say something.
얼굴이 왜 그 모양인가
하는거요?
Like why your face
is all cut up?
Look...
제가 이 마을에 처음 왔을 때
피터를 만나러
I told you when I first came
to this town
그 오두막에 갔었다고
얘기했었죠
that I went out to the cabin
to meet Peter,
그런데...
but that...
피터는 거기 없었구요...
that he wasn't there.
그런데 피터가 있었죠?
But he was, wasn't he?
네...
Yeah.
피터는 빚을 갚을 돈이
He-he told me
that he didn't have
없다고 했어요, 그래서...
the money he owed, so...
그래서 제가 내일
다시 온다고 했는데...
so I said I'd be back
the next day...
그리고 피터가
당신을 쐈죠
And he pulled a gun on you.
그걸 어떻게 알았어요?
How do you know this?
침실 옷장에서
이걸 꺼냈는데,
Because I brought this down
from our bedroom closet
총이 없더라구요
and found his gun missing.
총은 없는데,
총알은 전부 있네요
No gun, all the bullets.
그래서...
So...
알았군요
You know.
저도 믿기지 않네요
I didn't want to believe it.
남편은 당신이 자신을
죽여주길 원했어요
He needed you to kill him.
오늘 이 생명 보험증권을
찾았어요
I found this life
insurance policy today.
알겠지만,
좀 이상한 방식으로
You know, in some weird way,
남편은 절 지켜주려고
이 모든 일을 꾸민거 같아요
I think he did all this
to try to protect me.
자살을 하면,
법적 효력이 없기 때문이죠
'Cause this would be void
if he committed suicide.
정말..
정말 미안해요
I'm-I'm so sorry...
전부 다...
...for everything.
저도요...
Me, too.
바비, 당신이 알지도 못하는 사람들
위해서 희생한 거 알아요
Barbie, I've seen you sacrifice
yourself for total strangers.
근데 앞으로는,
더이상 거짓말 하지 말아요
But in the future,
there can be no more lies.
앞으로는?
In the future?
진심이에요?
You sure?
아마도요
Maybe.
이게..
그..
Is that...
알이야?
an egg?
주변에
미니 돔이 있어
With a mini-dome
around it.
이거 봐요
Hey, look.
애벌레가 고치가 됐어요
The caterpillar's
in a cocoon now.
번데기라고 하는거야
It's actually a chrysalis.
저런 샌님
He's a nerd.
그러니까 나도 여기
일부분이라는 거야?
And you think I'm supposed
to be part of this, too?
그래
Yeah.
우린 그렇게 생각해
We do.
세상에, 맙소사!
Oh, my God.
분홍별이야
It's the pink stars.
분홍별들이
별자리를 만들고 있어
And they're
making constellations.
아름답다...
It's... beautiful.
그런데...
이게 뭘 의미하는거지?
But... what does it mean?